<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Rentals on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/rentals/</link><description>Recent content in Rentals on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/rentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dating Apps: Privacy &amp; Security</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/dating-apps-privacy-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/dating-apps-privacy-security/</guid><description>Ah, finding love in the age of coronavirus&amp;hellip;
Did you know we offer subscription lines to over a dozen dating apps? Check out some of our current offerings below:
OkCupid Tinder Grindr Bumble Hinge Coffee Meets Bagel Zoosk BlackPeopleMeet Plenty of Fish MeetMe OurTime Coffee Meets Bagel MillionaireMatch Match.com We provide phone number rental subscriptions to all the major dating apps like OkCupid, Tinder, Grindr, Bumble, and Hinge.
Why use a rental phone number on a dating app?</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur: Single Service Temporary Numbers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/phoneblur-single-service-temporary-numbers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/phoneblur-single-service-temporary-numbers/</guid><description>Need a temporary number for a single service? Do you only require access to this number for a short amount of time? A temporary subscription plan could be the right choice for you!
Single service temporary numbers provide a US-based phone number for use on one designated service. You can rent these numbers in increments of one week or two weeks.
This service is offered as a temporary subscription plan: there are no renewals, no hassle, and no need to remember to top up your credit balance.</description></item><item><title>How Does Textverified Work?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</guid><description>When you sign up for Textverified, you can use credits to utilize services without giving away your personal phone number. We have real non-VoIP phone numbers from major US companies that allow you to register easily and quickly. Once you select a service, you will have 5 minutes to verify your account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t verify within the time limit, then your balance won&amp;rsquo;t be affected. Easy, right?
At Textverified, we are always acquiring new, reliable numbers to provide you with the most versatile solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>