<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>New Product on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/categories/new-product/</link><description>Recent content in New Product on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/categories/new-product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing: Free Numbers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</guid><description>Receive FREE SMS verifications from any online service using a Textverified temporary number. Try today for free!</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the release of a Chrome Extension for Textverified. This extension will allow better integrated of SMS verifications on any webpage, reducing the need to navigate to the main Textverified website. You can find the extension on our app.
Please note that this is a beta release. We aim to make the verification process easier than ever before, and your feedback will be invaluable to us as we work towards this goal.</description></item><item><title>Textverified Discord Bot</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</guid><description>Textverified has created a Discord bot that lets you use Textverified features through Discord. The first step to using the discord bot is to link your Textverified account to discord. This is done through your account settings on Textverified at https://www.textverified.com/Manage/Index. There will be a blue button that says &amp;ldquo;Login with Discord&amp;rdquo;, you can click that and it will bring you to discord&amp;rsquo;s site to do an oauth to link to Textverified.</description></item><item><title>Announcing Our New Android App!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/announcing-our-new-android-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/announcing-our-new-android-app/</guid><description>Enjoy a native mobile experience while using the same great verifications you&amp;rsquo;ve always had &amp;ndash; check it out!
Whether you just need one verification or you need &amp;rsquo;em in bulk, we&amp;rsquo;ve got your back. Non-VoIP, US numbers at your fingertips &amp;ndash; now you can even keep your privacy on the go.
Let us know what you think and if there are any other features we can bring to our mobile app.</description></item></channel></rss>