<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Rental on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/rental/</link><description>Recent content in Rental on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/rental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cyber Week: Staying Safe &amp; Avoiding Spam</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/cyber-week-staying-safe-avoiding-spam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/cyber-week-staying-safe-avoiding-spam/</guid><description>Happy Cyber Monday! Today marks the start of a week of awesome online deals for all you holiday shoppers out there.
Have you tried using one of our phone number rental subscriptions for your accounts with different online vendors? It&amp;rsquo;s always safer to avoid giving out your real phone number to various businesses, but did you know that we can also help you avoid spam messages?
This time of the year if you make a single purchase with an online merchant, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive tons of text messages from now until New Year&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Buying &amp; Selling</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</guid><description>At Textverified and Phoneblur, we&amp;rsquo;re all about protecting your privacy and personal data. If keeping your private phone number secure is your number one priority, then you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place.
Buying and selling items online is super easy when you&amp;rsquo;re shipping out a package or receiving one in the mail. But what if your transaction is happening offline?
Services like Craigslist and Facebook Marketplace have been popular for years.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Ride Shares</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</guid><description>Many of our users have been wondering about different uses for rental numbers. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about ride share services specifically.
Have you ever used Uber, Lyft, or even a ride share app for a traditional taxi company? Each of these services requires an active phone number before you can request a ride.
But if you use your personal phone number to register for a ride share app, then any driver who accepts your ride request will be able to see your number.</description></item></channel></rss>