<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Privacy on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/privacy/</link><description>Recent content in Privacy on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hassle-Free Way for Digital Nomads to Access US Services</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</guid><description>Digital nomads can access US services globally with Textverified: rent temp US phone numbers for your business, personal privacy, and more.</description></item><item><title>How to create an account for ANY online service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</guid><description>Receive SMS from any online service using Textverified temporary numbers. If a service is not listed, use &amp;#34;Service Not Listed&amp;#34; to get a verification from a less popular app.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Cashapp with a Temporary Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to receive 2FA SMS codes for Cashapp using a temporary phone number to safeguard your financial information online.</description></item><item><title>How to Register a WhatsApp Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and create an account for WhatsApp using a temporary phone number.</description></item><item><title>How to Sign Up for Telegram Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and receive SMS codes for Telegram using a temporary phone number to safeguard your information from exposure online.</description></item><item><title>Have You Been Pwned?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/have-you-been-pwned/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/have-you-been-pwned/</guid><description>At Textverified and Phoneblur, we care about protecting your privacy and security online. As part of our mission, we want to keep your personal information safe. Have you ever checked in on what&amp;rsquo;s out there about yourself?
We like to use the site &amp;ldquo;Have I Been Pwned?&amp;rdquo; to keep an eye on data breaches. Sometimes your private data will get leaked and you might not know about it until months (or even years!</description></item><item><title>Need Another Reason to Verify with Us?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/need-another-reason-to-verify-with-us/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/need-another-reason-to-verify-with-us/</guid><description>Recently one of our developers came across this article on Vice: &amp;ldquo;A Hacker Got All My Texts for $16&amp;rdquo;. In this piece, a journalist hires a hacker to show him just how easy it is to manipulate and re-route someone&amp;rsquo;s personal phone number using SMS authentication and phony user authorizations.
If this ever happens to you, your phone will seem completely normal &amp;ndash; at least until your apps stop working.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Ride Shares</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</guid><description>Many of our users have been wondering about different uses for rental numbers. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about ride share services specifically.
Have you ever used Uber, Lyft, or even a ride share app for a traditional taxi company? Each of these services requires an active phone number before you can request a ride.
But if you use your personal phone number to register for a ride share app, then any driver who accepts your ride request will be able to see your number.</description></item><item><title>Protect Your Privacy on Black Friday!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/protect-your-privacy-on-black-friday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/protect-your-privacy-on-black-friday/</guid><description>So you&amp;rsquo;re stuffed full of turkey and you&amp;rsquo;ve polished off that last slice of pecan pie. Now what?
It&amp;rsquo;s time to shop! But before you get to those Black Friday deals, how about renting a phone number on Textverified?
These days, many stores and merchants are asking for your phone number as part of the checkout process. But do you really want to give it to them?
Keeping your phone number private will decrease the number of spam messages you get.</description></item></channel></rss>