<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get an Uber account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Uber is a widely used ride-sharing service that makes transportation convenient. During the sign-up process for Uber, phone number verification is a necessary step. Simplify this process with Textverified, offering real US-based numbers for secure verification without disclosing your personal number.
Choosing Textverified with Uber ensures the privacy of your personal phone number, adding an extra layer of security to your ride-sharing experience. This protection shields you from potential unwanted messages or privacy concerns.</description></item><item><title>The Hassle-Free Way for Digital Nomads to Access US Services</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</guid><description>Digital nomads can access US services globally with Textverified: rent temp US phone numbers for your business, personal privacy, and more.</description></item><item><title>How to Make a PayPal Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-paypal-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-paypal-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Introduction Paypal is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most widespread ways to send money and get paid digitally. One setback of creating a PayPal account is that an active phone number is required to finish account creation. This can be a setback for those who don’t have a phone number or prefer not to give theirs out. There are a few ways that you can use to get around this issue, like getting a free number created online, but very few of these methods will actually work.</description></item><item><title>How to create an account for ANY online service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</guid><description>Receive SMS from any online service using Textverified temporary numbers. If a service is not listed, use &amp;#34;Service Not Listed&amp;#34; to get a verification from a less popular app.</description></item><item><title>Sign up for DoorDash without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/sign-up-for-doordash-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/sign-up-for-doordash-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to create a new DoorDash account to benefit from sign up rewards to save money and protect your online privacy.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Cashapp with a Temporary Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to receive 2FA SMS codes for Cashapp using a temporary phone number to safeguard your financial information online.</description></item><item><title>Guide: Sign up for Plenty of Fish Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/guide-sign-up-for-plenty-of-fish-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/guide-sign-up-for-plenty-of-fish-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide explains how to register your account on Plenty of Fish (POF) by using a Textverified, a temporary phone service, to protect your personal number.</description></item><item><title>How to Register a WhatsApp Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and create an account for WhatsApp using a temporary phone number.</description></item><item><title>How to get a Tinder account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-a-tinder-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-a-tinder-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide explains how to register a Tinder account without a phone number quickly and easily by receiving a one-time SMS verification with Textverified.</description></item><item><title>How to Sign Up for Telegram Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and receive SMS codes for Telegram using a temporary phone number to safeguard your information from exposure online.</description></item><item><title>How to Make a Coinbase Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-coinbase-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-coinbase-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Learn how to create a coinbase account with our US-based temporary phone numbers</description></item><item><title>How To Play LoL Clash Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-play-lol-clash-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-play-lol-clash-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>League of Legends (LoL) is a massively popular MOBA game. Riot Games recently released a new way to play LoL. LoL Clash allows players to create a team and compete with other teams in a tournament-like fashion. If you want to jump into this high-octane game mode, you’ll need to have a registered LoL account with an active phone number.
This restriction can be inconvenient for anyone concerned about keeping their personal information safe.</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Battle.net Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-battle.net-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-battle.net-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Battle.net is a service that allows you to play various online games like World of Warcraft, Overwatch 2, Diablo 3, and other games developed by Blizzard Entertainment. Making a Battle.net account requires an active mobile phone number. This can be problematic for users who don’t have an eligible phone number.
Luckily, there are ways to bypass this requirement. One popular method to get SMS verification is to use a virtual phone number.</description></item><item><title>How to create a Google Voice account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Google Voice is a phone service that allows you to use a number provided by google to send texts, calls, and voicemails. Making a Google Voice account will give you access to all of these features, but SMS verification is required to make an account. This can be problematic if you don’t want to provide your personal phone number to Google or if you don’t have an active phone number to create an account.</description></item><item><title>Uber / UberEats Verifications</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</guid><description>To decrease the issues you face when doing Uber / UberEats verifications, especially with regards to already used numbers, please follow these steps:
After obtaining the number to use from Textverified, please go to https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source and enter the number in. If the number is already used, the https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source site will notify you and a verification code will not be sent: You can then report the number and try again with a new number.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Week: Staying Safe &amp; Avoiding Spam</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/cyber-week-staying-safe-avoiding-spam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/cyber-week-staying-safe-avoiding-spam/</guid><description>Happy Cyber Monday! Today marks the start of a week of awesome online deals for all you holiday shoppers out there.
Have you tried using one of our phone number rental subscriptions for your accounts with different online vendors? It&amp;rsquo;s always safer to avoid giving out your real phone number to various businesses, but did you know that we can also help you avoid spam messages?
This time of the year if you make a single purchase with an online merchant, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive tons of text messages from now until New Year&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Dating Apps: Privacy &amp; Security</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/dating-apps-privacy-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/dating-apps-privacy-security/</guid><description>Ah, finding love in the age of coronavirus&amp;hellip;
Did you know we offer subscription lines to over a dozen dating apps? Check out some of our current offerings below:
OkCupid Tinder Grindr Bumble Hinge Coffee Meets Bagel Zoosk BlackPeopleMeet Plenty of Fish MeetMe OurTime Coffee Meets Bagel MillionaireMatch Match.com We provide phone number rental subscriptions to all the major dating apps like OkCupid, Tinder, Grindr, Bumble, and Hinge.
Why use a rental phone number on a dating app?</description></item><item><title>Uber Eats &amp; DoorDash: Save on Food Delivery</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-eats-doordash-save-on-food-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-eats-doordash-save-on-food-delivery/</guid><description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find the time to cook. Food delivery apps are a great way to get a good meal and support your local restaurants. DoorDash and Uber Eats are two of the most popular food delivery services out there.
When you set-up a temporary phone number rental service on Textverified or Phoneblur, you can register for multiple accounts on DoorDash and Uber Eats. With multiple DoorDash and Uber Eats accounts, you can take advantage of all the available promotions.</description></item><item><title>New Lower Prices!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/new-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/new-lower-prices/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, have you seen our new lower prices lately? We&amp;rsquo;ve cut prices by up to 40% on over 200 of our most popular services.
We know you have lots of options for your verifying needs, but we&amp;rsquo;d like you to stick around with us. With our new lower prices, you won&amp;rsquo;t have to choose between exceptional service and low-cost rentals. We still offer the same great service you&amp;rsquo;re used to, but with extremely competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur: Single Service Temporary Numbers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/phoneblur-single-service-temporary-numbers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/phoneblur-single-service-temporary-numbers/</guid><description>Need a temporary number for a single service? Do you only require access to this number for a short amount of time? A temporary subscription plan could be the right choice for you!
Single service temporary numbers provide a US-based phone number for use on one designated service. You can rent these numbers in increments of one week or two weeks.
This service is offered as a temporary subscription plan: there are no renewals, no hassle, and no need to remember to top up your credit balance.</description></item><item><title>Have You Been Pwned?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/have-you-been-pwned/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/have-you-been-pwned/</guid><description>At Textverified and Phoneblur, we care about protecting your privacy and security online. As part of our mission, we want to keep your personal information safe. Have you ever checked in on what&amp;rsquo;s out there about yourself?
We like to use the site &amp;ldquo;Have I Been Pwned?&amp;rdquo; to keep an eye on data breaches. Sometimes your private data will get leaked and you might not know about it until months (or even years!</description></item><item><title>Need Another Reason to Verify with Us?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/need-another-reason-to-verify-with-us/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/need-another-reason-to-verify-with-us/</guid><description>Recently one of our developers came across this article on Vice: &amp;ldquo;A Hacker Got All My Texts for $16&amp;rdquo;. In this piece, a journalist hires a hacker to show him just how easy it is to manipulate and re-route someone&amp;rsquo;s personal phone number using SMS authentication and phony user authorizations.
If this ever happens to you, your phone will seem completely normal &amp;ndash; at least until your apps stop working.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Buying &amp; Selling</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</guid><description>At Textverified and Phoneblur, we&amp;rsquo;re all about protecting your privacy and personal data. If keeping your private phone number secure is your number one priority, then you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place.
Buying and selling items online is super easy when you&amp;rsquo;re shipping out a package or receiving one in the mail. But what if your transaction is happening offline?
Services like Craigslist and Facebook Marketplace have been popular for years.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Long-Term Rental Number: Dating Apps</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-long-term-rental-number-dating-apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-long-term-rental-number-dating-apps/</guid><description>One of the most popular uses for phone number rental services is dating apps. Dating apps, like Tinder or Hinge, are a great way to test out our long-term rental services.
It&amp;rsquo;s good to be cautious when connecting with new people online. Although none of these apps will display your phone number to random users, you might decide you want to share your direct phone number with someone who seems promising.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Ride Shares</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</guid><description>Many of our users have been wondering about different uses for rental numbers. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about ride share services specifically.
Have you ever used Uber, Lyft, or even a ride share app for a traditional taxi company? Each of these services requires an active phone number before you can request a ride.
But if you use your personal phone number to register for a ride share app, then any driver who accepts your ride request will be able to see your number.</description></item><item><title>Protect Your Privacy on Black Friday!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/protect-your-privacy-on-black-friday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/protect-your-privacy-on-black-friday/</guid><description>So you&amp;rsquo;re stuffed full of turkey and you&amp;rsquo;ve polished off that last slice of pecan pie. Now what?
It&amp;rsquo;s time to shop! But before you get to those Black Friday deals, how about renting a phone number on Textverified?
These days, many stores and merchants are asking for your phone number as part of the checkout process. But do you really want to give it to them?
Keeping your phone number private will decrease the number of spam messages you get.</description></item><item><title>Crypto 103: Paying for a Purchase Order with Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-103-paying-for-a-purchase-order-with-bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-103-paying-for-a-purchase-order-with-bitcoin/</guid><description>Remember this screenshot from yesterday? This is your purchase order with Textverified.
Check out this blog post for a breakdown of your purchase order
Now we need to pay it! There are two convenient ways to send us your Bitcoin, i.e. pay your balance. First we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to pay via mobile device only and then we&amp;rsquo;ll cover QR codes in a separate post.
See that long string of letters and numbers?</description></item><item><title>Crypto 102: Sending Bitcoin &amp; Making Payments</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-102-sending-bitcoin-making-payments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-102-sending-bitcoin-making-payments/</guid><description>Yesterday we talked about opening a wallet on a digital currency exchange, like Coinbase. Then we used a debit account to add Bitcoin to your wallet.
Look at all that beautiful Bitcoin we bought yesterday!
Today we&amp;rsquo;re moving to the big leagues: activating the sending feature on your wallet and making a purchase order on Textverified &amp;ndash; and tomorrow we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about how to pay for your purchase order after you&amp;rsquo;ve received your payment invoice.</description></item><item><title>Crypto 101: How to Open a Wallet &amp; Buy Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-101-how-to-open-a-wallet-buy-bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/crypto-101-how-to-open-a-wallet-buy-bitcoin/</guid><description>At Textverified and our partner site, Phoneblur, the most popular payment method we offer is payment via cryptocurrency. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll give you a brief rundown on how to buy cryptocurrency, and in a follow-up post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain how to use cryptocurrency to make purchases on our sites.
Cryptocurrency is digital currency &amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s real money, but it&amp;rsquo;s exchanged completely online. At the moment, we accept bitcoin, the oldest and most well-established form of cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>Resurrect: How Does It Work?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/resurrect-how-does-it-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/resurrect-how-does-it-work/</guid><description>Looking to learn about our new Resurrect feature? You&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place!
Under your account, click on Verifications &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; History to view your previous verifications. If a verification is eligible for resurrection, there will be a &amp;ldquo;Resurrect&amp;rdquo; button under the Actions column. The button will then tell you how much it will cost to resurrect the number, which is often lower than the cost of doing a new verification entirely.</description></item><item><title>What is a Non-VoIP Number?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/what-is-a-non-voip-number/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/what-is-a-non-voip-number/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the basics. A non-VoIP number is a phone number that&amp;rsquo;s not tied to any one service provider or phone plan. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to use with internet phone services and helps keep your identity secure.
Why use a VoIP number? And what are text verification services anyway?
You may have noticed when signing up for a new account or service that sometimes companies will ask you to provide a phone number for either text or SMS verification.</description></item><item><title>How Does Textverified Work?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</guid><description>When you sign up for Textverified, you can use credits to utilize services without giving away your personal phone number. We have real non-VoIP phone numbers from major US companies that allow you to register easily and quickly. Once you select a service, you will have 5 minutes to verify your account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t verify within the time limit, then your balance won&amp;rsquo;t be affected. Easy, right?
At Textverified, we are always acquiring new, reliable numbers to provide you with the most versatile solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>