<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Credits on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/credits/</link><description>Recent content in Credits on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/credits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simplified Billing Cycle Renewal</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released an update to billing cycles to simplify renewals and the recovery of overdue rentals. With this update:
Billing cycles will now only automatically renew at the end of the cycle instead of a week in advance.
Rentals that fail to renew and become overdue can now be directly renewed and restored to their billing cycle from the Overdue Rentals page - you no longer need to renew from the billing cycle or reactivate them.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Third Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the third phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase, and this post for the second phase.
This third phase of the merge consists of migrating our rentals product to Textverified with a brand new and updated UI - you will no longer need to switch back and forth between the two sites for your verification needs.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Second Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the second phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase.
This second phase of the merge consists of combining two components: credit balances and credit orders/order history.
Credits balances associated with your account will be merged on both Textverified and Phoneblur. This means that your credit balance will be shared between both sites, so you will no longer have to manage your balance on both Textverified and Phoneblur when you consume our services.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we are in the process of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site. This consolidation will provide you with a more streamlined and improved experience. However, during this transition period, you will experience temporary redirects between the two sites.
This first phase of the merge consists of combining two key components: account information/access and the support ticket system.
Account information/access refers to pages related to logging in and managing your user account, such as changing passwords and setting up two-factor authentication (2FA).</description></item><item><title>Textverified Discord Bot</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</guid><description>Textverified has created a Discord bot that lets you use Textverified features through Discord. The first step to using the discord bot is to link your Textverified account to discord. This is done through your account settings on Textverified at https://www.textverified.com/Manage/Index. There will be a blue button that says &amp;ldquo;Login with Discord&amp;rdquo;, you can click that and it will bring you to discord&amp;rsquo;s site to do an oauth to link to Textverified.</description></item><item><title>Update: More Numbers, Better Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, a great new update is coming your way: we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to increase our supply of available phone number rental lines.
Starting with temporary single service, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see greater availability for rental numbers. Permanent multi-purpose lines will be up next, followed by permanent single service.
Now you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to buy larger quantities of number rentals from our rapidly-growing supply. We&amp;rsquo;ll be restocking popular numbers more frequently, and a bigger supply also means that maximum purchase allowances will increase.</description></item><item><title>New Payment Options for Textverified: Alipay</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</guid><description>Looking to purchase more credits for your Textverified account? We&amp;rsquo;ve recently added Alipay as a new payment option.
To use Alipay, log-in to your Textverified account and select the &amp;ldquo;Credit Card (USD)&amp;rdquo; payment option.
Click &amp;ldquo;Continue&amp;rdquo;. On the next page, you&amp;rsquo;ll see an option at the bottom to select Alipay.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve topped up your Textverified credits, remember that you can always transfer them to a linked Phoneblur account using our new Balance Transfer feature.</description></item><item><title>Now Accepting All Major Credit Cards</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/now-accepting-all-major-credit-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/now-accepting-all-major-credit-cards/</guid><description>Good news for Textverified users! We&amp;rsquo;ve recently integrated credit card payments from all major credit card providers.
When you add more credits to your account, you should now see a new option in our dropdown menu for &amp;ldquo;Credit Card (USD).&amp;rdquo;
If transaction speed if a big concern, we&amp;rsquo;re also excited to tell you that paying by credit card will usually process faster than Amazon Pay. We hope to expand this new payment option to Phoneblur next month.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Account Delegations</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</guid><description>Recently we received a great question from one of our users: can one &amp;ldquo;Parent&amp;rdquo; user account be used to manage multiple sub-accounts?
&amp;ldquo;Well, no,&amp;rdquo; we replied, &amp;ldquo;But why not?&amp;rdquo;
Our users know that when they send us good suggestions for improving Textverified, we&amp;rsquo;ll do everything we can to implement them! We are pleased to announce that we now offer account delegations as a new feature.
If you&amp;rsquo;re an employer running a big company, you probably want to make a single large purchase on Textverified.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Amazon Pay for Phoneblur</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-amazon-pay-for-phoneblur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-amazon-pay-for-phoneblur/</guid><description>You asked, we delivered: introducing Amazon Pay for Phoneblur! We are now accepting Amazon Pay payments for purchases of $20 or less. Just click the &amp;ldquo;Top Off&amp;rdquo; button on our home page.
Click through to confirm your Shopping Cart. Next you&amp;rsquo;ll see a page that looks like this:
Select your payment method. You can choose from Amazon Pay, Bitcoin, Ethereum, or Litecoin. Next, you can review your order:
Click &amp;ldquo;Checkout&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; if you&amp;rsquo;re using Amazon Pay, you&amp;rsquo;ll see this reminder notice:</description></item><item><title>New Payment Option: Amazon Pay</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-option-amazon-pay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-option-amazon-pay/</guid><description>Lately we&amp;rsquo;ve received some feedback from our users asking for a credit card payment option. We hear you and we agree &amp;ndash; so today we&amp;rsquo;re introducing Amazon Pay for Textverified. We&amp;rsquo;ll also be adding Amazon Pay to PhoneBlur soon.
Amazon Pay is a great option for small bundle purchases if you don&amp;rsquo;t use crypto currency &amp;ndash; but since we&amp;rsquo;ll be processing payments through third party credit card companies, we do need to add a small percentage surcharge to any Amazon Pay purchases.</description></item></channel></rss>