<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>New Feature on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/categories/new-feature/</link><description>Recent content in New Feature on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/categories/new-feature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Feature: How to Receive SMS and Voice Calls for an AdGate Rental</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</guid><description>New: Same line SMS and Voice Rentals We’re excited to announce the release of a long requested feature!
You can now verify your AdGate accounts on the same line with SMS and/or voice with our number rentals. This means that you will no longer purchase AdGate verifications – instead, you will purchase the AdGate service on our rentals.
This feature is still in beta and we have limited supply. Please give us any feedback or comments you may have.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Balance Transfers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-balance-transfers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-balance-transfers/</guid><description>Yesterday we explained how to link a Phoneblur account to a Textverified account and vice-versa. Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to show you how to do a balance transfer of credits between two linked accounts.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a Phoneblur account with $25.01 in credit. Let&amp;rsquo;s transfer $10 to a linked Textverified account.
Step 1: Under the &amp;ldquo;Platform-Link&amp;rdquo; button, click &amp;ldquo;Balance Transfers&amp;rdquo;
Step 2: Enter the amount of credits you would like to transfer</description></item><item><title>Site Update: Connect Your TV and PB Accounts</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</guid><description>We know you love us so much that you probably have a Textverified account and a Phoneblur account. Now the update you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for is finally here: starting today, you can link your Textverified account and your Phoneblur account!
How to Link Accounts:
Step 1: Log-in to both your Phoneblur account and your Textverified account. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a Phoneblur account for this tutorial, but the process is the same from either account.</description></item><item><title>New Textverified Feature: Simultaneous Pending Verifications</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-textverified-feature-simultaneous-pending-verifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-textverified-feature-simultaneous-pending-verifications/</guid><description>Ever wished you could start a new Textverified verification while your current one is &amp;ldquo;pending&amp;rdquo;? When you initiate a new verification, you receive a certain amount of time to access your verification code.
Sometimes you may want to start a second verification, but you&amp;rsquo;re stuck waiting for the timer to run down on your first verification.
Now you can have two &amp;ldquo;pending&amp;rdquo; verifications active at the same time!
If you purchase $50 in credit via Textverified, this option will be available to you immediately &amp;ndash; you can do this in a single transaction, or multiple smaller transactions that add up to $50.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur Feature: Requesting A Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</guid><description>Did you know you can make requests for popular services? We now offer this feature for both temporary and permanent rentals.
Sometimes you might require a specific service that is currently unavailable on our sites. This service will show up under our service listings, but when you click &amp;ldquo;Add,&amp;rdquo; you will be taken to a provisioning request page.
On the provisioning request page, you will be able to request the service and pay for it: we&amp;rsquo;ll either get the service up and running in three days or we&amp;rsquo;ll refund your money.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Account Delegations</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</guid><description>Recently we received a great question from one of our users: can one &amp;ldquo;Parent&amp;rdquo; user account be used to manage multiple sub-accounts?
&amp;ldquo;Well, no,&amp;rdquo; we replied, &amp;ldquo;But why not?&amp;rdquo;
Our users know that when they send us good suggestions for improving Textverified, we&amp;rsquo;ll do everything we can to implement them! We are pleased to announce that we now offer account delegations as a new feature.
If you&amp;rsquo;re an employer running a big company, you probably want to make a single large purchase on Textverified.</description></item></channel></rss>