<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Textverified on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/textverified/</link><description>Recent content in Textverified on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/textverified/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing: Free Numbers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</guid><description>Receive FREE SMS verifications from any online service using a Textverified temporary number. Try today for free!</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension Release Announced</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-release-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:07:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-release-announced/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share that our Textverified Chrome Extension has completed its beta phase! After thorough testing and valuable feedback from our amazing users like you, we&amp;rsquo;re proud to present a polished and reliable extension that&amp;rsquo;s ready to streamline your verification process. We&amp;rsquo;ll be releasing the extension officially later this week. What&amp;rsquo;s new in this update:
1. Verification Functionality Improvements We&amp;rsquo;ve added the ability for users to reuse a previously verified number to complete another verification.</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension Improvements</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-improvements/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:07:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-improvements/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that we have some fantastic UI improvements and flow enhancements in the works for our Chrome Extension for Textverified! We have updated the extension to look more like our verification interface on our website. Pricing will start to be shown after you type in the service in the search bar
Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneakpeak of what&amp;rsquo;s to come:
Streamlined Interface: Get ready for a sleeker and more intuitive interface that will make navigating the extension a breeze.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Third Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the third phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase, and this post for the second phase.
This third phase of the merge consists of migrating our rentals product to Textverified with a brand new and updated UI - you will no longer need to switch back and forth between the two sites for your verification needs.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Second Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the second phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase.
This second phase of the merge consists of combining two components: credit balances and credit orders/order history.
Credits balances associated with your account will be merged on both Textverified and Phoneblur. This means that your credit balance will be shared between both sites, so you will no longer have to manage your balance on both Textverified and Phoneblur when you consume our services.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we are in the process of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site. This consolidation will provide you with a more streamlined and improved experience. However, during this transition period, you will experience temporary redirects between the two sites.
This first phase of the merge consists of combining two key components: account information/access and the support ticket system.
Account information/access refers to pages related to logging in and managing your user account, such as changing passwords and setting up two-factor authentication (2FA).</description></item><item><title>Update: More Numbers, Better Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, a great new update is coming your way: we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to increase our supply of available phone number rental lines.
Starting with temporary single service, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see greater availability for rental numbers. Permanent multi-purpose lines will be up next, followed by permanent single service.
Now you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to buy larger quantities of number rentals from our rapidly-growing supply. We&amp;rsquo;ll be restocking popular numbers more frequently, and a bigger supply also means that maximum purchase allowances will increase.</description></item><item><title>New Payment Options for Textverified: Alipay</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</guid><description>Looking to purchase more credits for your Textverified account? We&amp;rsquo;ve recently added Alipay as a new payment option.
To use Alipay, log-in to your Textverified account and select the &amp;ldquo;Credit Card (USD)&amp;rdquo; payment option.
Click &amp;ldquo;Continue&amp;rdquo;. On the next page, you&amp;rsquo;ll see an option at the bottom to select Alipay.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve topped up your Textverified credits, remember that you can always transfer them to a linked Phoneblur account using our new Balance Transfer feature.</description></item><item><title>Site Update: Connect Your TV and PB Accounts</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</guid><description>We know you love us so much that you probably have a Textverified account and a Phoneblur account. Now the update you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for is finally here: starting today, you can link your Textverified account and your Phoneblur account!
How to Link Accounts:
Step 1: Log-in to both your Phoneblur account and your Textverified account. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a Phoneblur account for this tutorial, but the process is the same from either account.</description></item><item><title>Textverified: Features Page</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</guid><description>More big news for our Textverified users: we now have a concise, easy-to-read Features page up on our site!
If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Textverified, check it out for a good overview of how to get started. You&amp;rsquo;ll see information about temporary number rentals, all our additional features, and our app.
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve been with us for awhile, you can learn about some of our more advanced features, like sub-account delegations or Resurrect.</description></item></channel></rss>