<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Rentals on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/rentals/</link><description>Recent content in Rentals on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/rentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the release of a Chrome Extension for Textverified. This extension will allow better integrated of SMS verifications on any webpage, reducing the need to navigate to the main Textverified website. You can find the extension on our app.
Please note that this is a beta release. We aim to make the verification process easier than ever before, and your feedback will be invaluable to us as we work towards this goal.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: How to Receive SMS and Voice Calls for an AdGate Rental</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</guid><description>New: Same line SMS and Voice Rentals We’re excited to announce the release of a long requested feature!
You can now verify your AdGate accounts on the same line with SMS and/or voice with our number rentals. This means that you will no longer purchase AdGate verifications – instead, you will purchase the AdGate service on our rentals.
This feature is still in beta and we have limited supply. Please give us any feedback or comments you may have.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Billing Cycle Renewal</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released an update to billing cycles to simplify renewals and the recovery of overdue rentals. With this update:
Billing cycles will now only automatically renew at the end of the cycle instead of a week in advance.
Rentals that fail to renew and become overdue can now be directly renewed and restored to their billing cycle from the Overdue Rentals page - you no longer need to renew from the billing cycle or reactivate them.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Third Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the third phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase, and this post for the second phase.
This third phase of the merge consists of migrating our rentals product to Textverified with a brand new and updated UI - you will no longer need to switch back and forth between the two sites for your verification needs.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Second Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the second phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase.
This second phase of the merge consists of combining two components: credit balances and credit orders/order history.
Credits balances associated with your account will be merged on both Textverified and Phoneblur. This means that your credit balance will be shared between both sites, so you will no longer have to manage your balance on both Textverified and Phoneblur when you consume our services.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we are in the process of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site. This consolidation will provide you with a more streamlined and improved experience. However, during this transition period, you will experience temporary redirects between the two sites.
This first phase of the merge consists of combining two key components: account information/access and the support ticket system.
Account information/access refers to pages related to logging in and managing your user account, such as changing passwords and setting up two-factor authentication (2FA).</description></item><item><title>Shorter Rentals and Instant Availability</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/shorter-rentals-and-instant-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/shorter-rentals-and-instant-availability/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce that we are now selling shorter temporary numbers (1 day and 3 day) as well as offering the option of buying any of our products with instant availability (no need to ever hit Wake Up before using your line).
Shorter Rentals
In addition to being able to purchase a number for a single service for one week or two weeks, you now have the option to reserve a line for only one or three days for a reduced price.</description></item><item><title>Update: More Numbers, Better Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, a great new update is coming your way: we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to increase our supply of available phone number rental lines.
Starting with temporary single service, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see greater availability for rental numbers. Permanent multi-purpose lines will be up next, followed by permanent single service.
Now you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to buy larger quantities of number rentals from our rapidly-growing supply. We&amp;rsquo;ll be restocking popular numbers more frequently, and a bigger supply also means that maximum purchase allowances will increase.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur Feature: Requesting A Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</guid><description>Did you know you can make requests for popular services? We now offer this feature for both temporary and permanent rentals.
Sometimes you might require a specific service that is currently unavailable on our sites. This service will show up under our service listings, but when you click &amp;ldquo;Add,&amp;rdquo; you will be taken to a provisioning request page.
On the provisioning request page, you will be able to request the service and pay for it: we&amp;rsquo;ll either get the service up and running in three days or we&amp;rsquo;ll refund your money.</description></item><item><title>Textverified: Features Page</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</guid><description>More big news for our Textverified users: we now have a concise, easy-to-read Features page up on our site!
If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Textverified, check it out for a good overview of how to get started. You&amp;rsquo;ll see information about temporary number rentals, all our additional features, and our app.
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve been with us for awhile, you can learn about some of our more advanced features, like sub-account delegations or Resurrect.</description></item><item><title>From Textverified to Phoneblur: Phone Number Rentals are Moving!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/from-textverified-to-phoneblur-phone-number-rentals-are-moving/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/from-textverified-to-phoneblur-phone-number-rentals-are-moving/</guid><description>Exciting news here at Textverified: phone number rentals are moving to our new service, Phoneblur. We have been hard at work bringing you a great new way to rent numbers &amp;ndash; and we even have an Android app!
We know you love Textverified, and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping you&amp;rsquo;ll love Phoneblur too. If you&amp;rsquo;re already familiar with renting phone numbers via Textverified, then you won&amp;rsquo;t notice too many changes over at Phoneblur.</description></item></channel></rss>