<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Text-Verified on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/text-verified/</link><description>Recent content in Text-Verified on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/text-verified/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Make a Coinbase Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-coinbase-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-coinbase-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Learn how to create a coinbase account with our US-based temporary phone numbers</description></item><item><title>How To Play LoL Clash Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-play-lol-clash-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-play-lol-clash-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>League of Legends (LoL) is a massively popular MOBA game. Riot Games recently released a new way to play LoL. LoL Clash allows players to create a team and compete with other teams in a tournament-like fashion. If you want to jump into this high-octane game mode, you’ll need to have a registered LoL account with an active phone number.
This restriction can be inconvenient for anyone concerned about keeping their personal information safe.</description></item><item><title>How to create a Google Voice account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Google Voice is a phone service that allows you to use a number provided by google to send texts, calls, and voicemails. Making a Google Voice account will give you access to all of these features, but SMS verification is required to make an account. This can be problematic if you don’t want to provide your personal phone number to Google or if you don’t have an active phone number to create an account.</description></item></channel></rss>