<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Verification on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/verification/</link><description>Recent content in Verification on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/verification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get an Uber account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Uber is a widely used ride-sharing service that makes transportation convenient. During the sign-up process for Uber, phone number verification is a necessary step. Simplify this process with Textverified, offering real US-based numbers for secure verification without disclosing your personal number.
Choosing Textverified with Uber ensures the privacy of your personal phone number, adding an extra layer of security to your ride-sharing experience. This protection shields you from potential unwanted messages or privacy concerns.</description></item><item><title>How to Make a PayPal Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-paypal-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-make-a-paypal-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Introduction Paypal is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most widespread ways to send money and get paid digitally. One setback of creating a PayPal account is that an active phone number is required to finish account creation. This can be a setback for those who don’t have a phone number or prefer not to give theirs out. There are a few ways that you can use to get around this issue, like getting a free number created online, but very few of these methods will actually work.</description></item><item><title>Sign up for DoorDash without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/sign-up-for-doordash-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/sign-up-for-doordash-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to create a new DoorDash account to benefit from sign up rewards to save money and protect your online privacy.</description></item><item><title>How to Use Cashapp with a Temporary Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-use-cashapp-with-a-temporary-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to receive 2FA SMS codes for Cashapp using a temporary phone number to safeguard your financial information online.</description></item><item><title>Guide: Sign up for Plenty of Fish Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/guide-sign-up-for-plenty-of-fish-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/guide-sign-up-for-plenty-of-fish-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide explains how to register your account on Plenty of Fish (POF) by using a Textverified, a temporary phone service, to protect your personal number.</description></item><item><title>How to Register a WhatsApp Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-register-a-whatsapp-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and create an account for WhatsApp using a temporary phone number.</description></item><item><title>How to get a Tinder account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-a-tinder-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-a-tinder-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide explains how to register a Tinder account without a phone number quickly and easily by receiving a one-time SMS verification with Textverified.</description></item><item><title>How to Sign Up for Telegram Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-sign-up-for-telegram-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>This guide will show you how to register and receive SMS codes for Telegram using a temporary phone number to safeguard your information from exposure online.</description></item><item><title>How to create a Google Voice account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-google-voice-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Google Voice is a phone service that allows you to use a number provided by google to send texts, calls, and voicemails. Making a Google Voice account will give you access to all of these features, but SMS verification is required to make an account. This can be problematic if you don’t want to provide your personal phone number to Google or if you don’t have an active phone number to create an account.</description></item><item><title>Uber / UberEats Verifications</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</guid><description>To decrease the issues you face when doing Uber / UberEats verifications, especially with regards to already used numbers, please follow these steps:
After obtaining the number to use from Textverified, please go to https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source and enter the number in. If the number is already used, the https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source site will notify you and a verification code will not be sent: You can then report the number and try again with a new number.</description></item><item><title>Resurrect: How Does It Work?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/resurrect-how-does-it-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/resurrect-how-does-it-work/</guid><description>Looking to learn about our new Resurrect feature? You&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place!
Under your account, click on Verifications &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; History to view your previous verifications. If a verification is eligible for resurrection, there will be a &amp;ldquo;Resurrect&amp;rdquo; button under the Actions column. The button will then tell you how much it will cost to resurrect the number, which is often lower than the cost of doing a new verification entirely.</description></item></channel></rss>