<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Textverified on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/textverified/</link><description>Recent content in Textverified on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/textverified/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hassle-Free Way for Digital Nomads to Access US Services</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/the-hassle-free-way-for-digital-nomads-to-access-us-services/</guid><description>Digital nomads can access US services globally with Textverified: rent temp US phone numbers for your business, personal privacy, and more.</description></item><item><title>How to create an account for ANY online service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-an-account-for-any-online-service/</guid><description>Receive SMS from any online service using Textverified temporary numbers. If a service is not listed, use &amp;#34;Service Not Listed&amp;#34; to get a verification from a less popular app.</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Battle.net Account Without a Phone Number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-battle.net-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-create-a-battle.net-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Battle.net is a service that allows you to play various online games like World of Warcraft, Overwatch 2, Diablo 3, and other games developed by Blizzard Entertainment. Making a Battle.net account requires an active mobile phone number. This can be problematic for users who don’t have an eligible phone number.
Luckily, there are ways to bypass this requirement. One popular method to get SMS verification is to use a virtual phone number.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Buying &amp; Selling</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-buying-selling/</guid><description>At Textverified and Phoneblur, we&amp;rsquo;re all about protecting your privacy and personal data. If keeping your private phone number secure is your number one priority, then you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place.
Buying and selling items online is super easy when you&amp;rsquo;re shipping out a package or receiving one in the mail. But what if your transaction is happening offline?
Services like Craigslist and Facebook Marketplace have been popular for years.</description></item><item><title>How Does Textverified Work?</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-does-textverified-work/</guid><description>When you sign up for Textverified, you can use credits to utilize services without giving away your personal phone number. We have real non-VoIP phone numbers from major US companies that allow you to register easily and quickly. Once you select a service, you will have 5 minutes to verify your account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t verify within the time limit, then your balance won&amp;rsquo;t be affected. Easy, right?
At Textverified, we are always acquiring new, reliable numbers to provide you with the most versatile solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>