<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Merge on Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/merge/</link><description>Recent content in Merge on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/tags/merge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Third Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the third phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase, and this post for the second phase.
This third phase of the merge consists of migrating our rentals product to Textverified with a brand new and updated UI - you will no longer need to switch back and forth between the two sites for your verification needs.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Second Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the second phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase.
This second phase of the merge consists of combining two components: credit balances and credit orders/order history.
Credits balances associated with your account will be merged on both Textverified and Phoneblur. This means that your credit balance will be shared between both sites, so you will no longer have to manage your balance on both Textverified and Phoneblur when you consume our services.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we are in the process of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site. This consolidation will provide you with a more streamlined and improved experience. However, during this transition period, you will experience temporary redirects between the two sites.
This first phase of the merge consists of combining two key components: account information/access and the support ticket system.
Account information/access refers to pages related to logging in and managing your user account, such as changing passwords and setting up two-factor authentication (2FA).</description></item><item><title>Site Update: Connect Your TV and PB Accounts</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</guid><description>We know you love us so much that you probably have a Textverified account and a Phoneblur account. Now the update you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for is finally here: starting today, you can link your Textverified account and your Phoneblur account!
How to Link Accounts:
Step 1: Log-in to both your Phoneblur account and your Textverified account. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a Phoneblur account for this tutorial, but the process is the same from either account.</description></item></channel></rss>