<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Textverified Updates</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/</link><description>Recent content on Textverified Updates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing: Free Numbers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-free-numbers/</guid><description>Receive FREE SMS verifications from any online service using a Textverified temporary number. Try today for free!</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension Release Announced</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-release-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 09:07:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-release-announced/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share that our Textverified Chrome Extension has completed its beta phase! After thorough testing and valuable feedback from our amazing users like you, we&amp;rsquo;re proud to present a polished and reliable extension that&amp;rsquo;s ready to streamline your verification process. We&amp;rsquo;ll be releasing the extension officially later this week. What&amp;rsquo;s new in this update:
1. Verification Functionality Improvements We&amp;rsquo;ve added the ability for users to reuse a previously verified number to complete another verification.</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension Improvements</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-improvements/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 09:07:47 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension-improvements/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that we have some fantastic UI improvements and flow enhancements in the works for our Chrome Extension for Textverified! We have updated the extension to look more like our verification interface on our website. Pricing will start to be shown after you type in the service in the search bar
Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneakpeak of what&amp;rsquo;s to come:
Streamlined Interface: Get ready for a sleeker and more intuitive interface that will make navigating the extension a breeze.</description></item><item><title>Textverified Chrome Extension</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-chrome-extension/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the release of a Chrome Extension for Textverified. This extension will allow better integrated of SMS verifications on any webpage, reducing the need to navigate to the main Textverified website. You can find the extension on our app.
Please note that this is a beta release. We aim to make the verification process easier than ever before, and your feedback will be invaluable to us as we work towards this goal.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: How to Receive SMS and Voice Calls for an AdGate Rental</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-how-to-receive-sms-and-voice-calls-for-an-adgate-rental/</guid><description>New: Same line SMS and Voice Rentals We’re excited to announce the release of a long requested feature!
You can now verify your AdGate accounts on the same line with SMS and/or voice with our number rentals. This means that you will no longer purchase AdGate verifications – instead, you will purchase the AdGate service on our rentals.
This feature is still in beta and we have limited supply. Please give us any feedback or comments you may have.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Billing Cycle Renewal</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/simplified-billing-cycle-renewal/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve released an update to billing cycles to simplify renewals and the recovery of overdue rentals. With this update:
Billing cycles will now only automatically renew at the end of the cycle instead of a week in advance.
Rentals that fail to renew and become overdue can now be directly renewed and restored to their billing cycle from the Overdue Rentals page - you no longer need to renew from the billing cycle or reactivate them.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Third Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-third-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the third phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase, and this post for the second phase.
This third phase of the merge consists of migrating our rentals product to Textverified with a brand new and updated UI - you will no longer need to switch back and forth between the two sites for your verification needs.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Second Phase Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-second-phase-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that the second phase of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site has been released. Please refer to this post regarding the first phase.
This second phase of the merge consists of combining two components: credit balances and credit orders/order history.
Credits balances associated with your account will be merged on both Textverified and Phoneblur. This means that your credit balance will be shared between both sites, so you will no longer have to manage your balance on both Textverified and Phoneblur when you consume our services.</description></item><item><title>Textverified and Phoneblur Merge</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-and-phoneblur-merge/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we are in the process of merging Textverified and Phoneblur into one site. This consolidation will provide you with a more streamlined and improved experience. However, during this transition period, you will experience temporary redirects between the two sites.
This first phase of the merge consists of combining two key components: account information/access and the support ticket system.
Account information/access refers to pages related to logging in and managing your user account, such as changing passwords and setting up two-factor authentication (2FA).</description></item><item><title>Subscription Renewal Improvements: Automatic Retries</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/subscription-renewal-improvements-automatic-retries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/subscription-renewal-improvements-automatic-retries/</guid><description>We have made some updates to subscription renewal, including a highly requested feature: automatic subscription renewal retries! If renewal fails and you top up your account, but forget to manually renew your subscription, we&amp;rsquo;ll take care of it for you. We&amp;rsquo;ll attempt a second renewal before your subscription expires. Note that this will only occur for new subscriptions or subscriptions that have successfully renewed after October 18th, 2022.
There are also other smaller changes related to renewal that have been made, which are detailed below:</description></item><item><title>Shorter Rentals and Instant Availability</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/shorter-rentals-and-instant-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/shorter-rentals-and-instant-availability/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce that we are now selling shorter temporary numbers (1 day and 3 day) as well as offering the option of buying any of our products with instant availability (no need to ever hit Wake Up before using your line).
Shorter Rentals
In addition to being able to purchase a number for a single service for one week or two weeks, you now have the option to reserve a line for only one or three days for a reduced price.</description></item><item><title>Textverified Discord Bot</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-discord-bot/</guid><description>Textverified has created a Discord bot that lets you use Textverified features through Discord. The first step to using the discord bot is to link your Textverified account to discord. This is done through your account settings on Textverified at https://www.textverified.com/Manage/Index. There will be a blue button that says &amp;ldquo;Login with Discord&amp;rdquo;, you can click that and it will bring you to discord&amp;rsquo;s site to do an oauth to link to Textverified.</description></item><item><title>Update: More Numbers, Better Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/update-more-numbers-better-service/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, a great new update is coming your way: we&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to increase our supply of available phone number rental lines.
Starting with temporary single service, you&amp;rsquo;ll soon see greater availability for rental numbers. Permanent multi-purpose lines will be up next, followed by permanent single service.
Now you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to buy larger quantities of number rentals from our rapidly-growing supply. We&amp;rsquo;ll be restocking popular numbers more frequently, and a bigger supply also means that maximum purchase allowances will increase.</description></item><item><title>New Payment Options for Textverified: Alipay</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-options-for-textverified-alipay/</guid><description>Looking to purchase more credits for your Textverified account? We&amp;rsquo;ve recently added Alipay as a new payment option.
To use Alipay, log-in to your Textverified account and select the &amp;ldquo;Credit Card (USD)&amp;rdquo; payment option.
Click &amp;ldquo;Continue&amp;rdquo;. On the next page, you&amp;rsquo;ll see an option at the bottom to select Alipay.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve topped up your Textverified credits, remember that you can always transfer them to a linked Phoneblur account using our new Balance Transfer feature.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Balance Transfers</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-balance-transfers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-balance-transfers/</guid><description>Yesterday we explained how to link a Phoneblur account to a Textverified account and vice-versa. Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to show you how to do a balance transfer of credits between two linked accounts.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a Phoneblur account with $25.01 in credit. Let&amp;rsquo;s transfer $10 to a linked Textverified account.
Step 1: Under the &amp;ldquo;Platform-Link&amp;rdquo; button, click &amp;ldquo;Balance Transfers&amp;rdquo;
Step 2: Enter the amount of credits you would like to transfer</description></item><item><title>Site Update: Connect Your TV and PB Accounts</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/site-update-connect-your-tv-and-pb-accounts/</guid><description>We know you love us so much that you probably have a Textverified account and a Phoneblur account. Now the update you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for is finally here: starting today, you can link your Textverified account and your Phoneblur account!
How to Link Accounts:
Step 1: Log-in to both your Phoneblur account and your Textverified account. We&amp;rsquo;ll use a Phoneblur account for this tutorial, but the process is the same from either account.</description></item><item><title>New Textverified Feature: Simultaneous Pending Verifications</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-textverified-feature-simultaneous-pending-verifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-textverified-feature-simultaneous-pending-verifications/</guid><description>Ever wished you could start a new Textverified verification while your current one is &amp;ldquo;pending&amp;rdquo;? When you initiate a new verification, you receive a certain amount of time to access your verification code.
Sometimes you may want to start a second verification, but you&amp;rsquo;re stuck waiting for the timer to run down on your first verification.
Now you can have two &amp;ldquo;pending&amp;rdquo; verifications active at the same time!
If you purchase $50 in credit via Textverified, this option will be available to you immediately &amp;ndash; you can do this in a single transaction, or multiple smaller transactions that add up to $50.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur: Changes to Message Handling</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-changes-to-message-handling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-changes-to-message-handling/</guid><description>We are rolling out new changes to how you can view and receive your messages for lines you have rented on Phoneblur. In addition to the view of all your messages, you can also view just your messages for a specific subscription or the messages for a specific line in one of your subscriptions. This enables you to just see the messages you currently care about.
Viewing Your Messages
The easiest way to view all the messages all your lines have received is to click &amp;ldquo;Messages&amp;rdquo; in the top bar:</description></item><item><title>New Lower Prices!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-lower-prices/</guid><description>Hey Textverified and Phoneblur users, have you seen our new lower prices lately? We&amp;rsquo;ve cut prices by up to 40% on over 200 of our most popular services.
We know you have lots of options for your verifying needs, but we&amp;rsquo;d like you to stick around with us. With our new lower prices, you won&amp;rsquo;t have to choose between exceptional service and low-cost rentals. We still offer the same great service you&amp;rsquo;re used to, but with extremely competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur Feature: Requesting A Service</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-feature-requesting-a-service/</guid><description>Did you know you can make requests for popular services? We now offer this feature for both temporary and permanent rentals.
Sometimes you might require a specific service that is currently unavailable on our sites. This service will show up under our service listings, but when you click &amp;ldquo;Add,&amp;rdquo; you will be taken to a provisioning request page.
On the provisioning request page, you will be able to request the service and pay for it: we&amp;rsquo;ll either get the service up and running in three days or we&amp;rsquo;ll refund your money.</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur: Multiple Permanent Subscriptions</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-multiple-permanent-subscriptions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-multiple-permanent-subscriptions/</guid><description>Did you know that you can hold multiple permanent subscriptions under a single Phoneblur account?
When you purchase a new permanent rental service or whole line, you can choose whether you want to add it to your Primary subscription or if you&amp;rsquo;d like to create a new subscription.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a screenshot of an account with a single permanent subscription for Coinbase:
Now we&amp;rsquo;re going to add a second permanent subscription to Instagram:</description></item><item><title>Phoneblur: Features Page</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-features-page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/phoneblur-features-page/</guid><description>Hey Phoneblur users, you know we&amp;rsquo;d never forget about you! Here&amp;rsquo;s the comprehensive Features page you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got information on all of our Subscription Plans, a ton of Add-On Features, and our Android App. Drop us a line if you think we&amp;rsquo;ve missed something and we&amp;rsquo;ll add it in.
Happy verifiying!</description></item><item><title>Textverified: Features Page</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/textverified-features-page/</guid><description>More big news for our Textverified users: we now have a concise, easy-to-read Features page up on our site!
If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Textverified, check it out for a good overview of how to get started. You&amp;rsquo;ll see information about temporary number rentals, all our additional features, and our app.
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve been with us for awhile, you can learn about some of our more advanced features, like sub-account delegations or Resurrect.</description></item><item><title>Now Accepting All Major Credit Cards</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/now-accepting-all-major-credit-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/now-accepting-all-major-credit-cards/</guid><description>Good news for Textverified users! We&amp;rsquo;ve recently integrated credit card payments from all major credit card providers.
When you add more credits to your account, you should now see a new option in our dropdown menu for &amp;ldquo;Credit Card (USD).&amp;rdquo;
If transaction speed if a big concern, we&amp;rsquo;re also excited to tell you that paying by credit card will usually process faster than Amazon Pay. We hope to expand this new payment option to Phoneblur next month.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Account Delegations</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-account-delegations/</guid><description>Recently we received a great question from one of our users: can one &amp;ldquo;Parent&amp;rdquo; user account be used to manage multiple sub-accounts?
&amp;ldquo;Well, no,&amp;rdquo; we replied, &amp;ldquo;But why not?&amp;rdquo;
Our users know that when they send us good suggestions for improving Textverified, we&amp;rsquo;ll do everything we can to implement them! We are pleased to announce that we now offer account delegations as a new feature.
If you&amp;rsquo;re an employer running a big company, you probably want to make a single large purchase on Textverified.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Amazon Pay for Phoneblur</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-amazon-pay-for-phoneblur/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/introducing-amazon-pay-for-phoneblur/</guid><description>You asked, we delivered: introducing Amazon Pay for Phoneblur! We are now accepting Amazon Pay payments for purchases of $20 or less. Just click the &amp;ldquo;Top Off&amp;rdquo; button on our home page.
Click through to confirm your Shopping Cart. Next you&amp;rsquo;ll see a page that looks like this:
Select your payment method. You can choose from Amazon Pay, Bitcoin, Ethereum, or Litecoin. Next, you can review your order:
Click &amp;ldquo;Checkout&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; if you&amp;rsquo;re using Amazon Pay, you&amp;rsquo;ll see this reminder notice:</description></item><item><title>Updates for Textverified</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/updates-for-textverified/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/updates-for-textverified/</guid><description>Hello Textverified users! We&amp;rsquo;ve recently launched some exciting new updates and wanted to tell you about them:
Textverified Search Bar &amp;ndash; We&amp;rsquo;ve made some improvements to our search bar on the &amp;ldquo;Text &amp;amp; SMS&amp;rdquo; Verifications page. Now if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a specific service, you can find it directly by using our &amp;ldquo;Short-term / temporary numbers&amp;rdquo; search bar. (Please note that you are no longer able to search the full verifications page via &amp;ldquo;ctrl + f&amp;rdquo;)</description></item><item><title>System Upgrade</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/system-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/system-upgrade/</guid><description>Please bear with us as we roll out a new enhancement to improve out site stability and speed today.
And as always please send us a message if you notice any problems with your verifications and we&amp;rsquo;ll do our best to fix it quickly.</description></item><item><title>New Feature: Resurrect</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-resurrect/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-feature-resurrect/</guid><description>Today we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce a new text verification feature: Resurrect.
Over the last few months, we&amp;rsquo;ve heard from many users who wanted an option to reuse old verification phone numbers. Now you can with Resurrect.
Before Resurrect, users could reuse phone numbers for about two minutes immediately after the initial activation. But if you needed to reverify a few hours later, you&amp;rsquo;d be stuck.
With Resurrect, you now have the option to resurrect a phone number as long as it is still available within our database.</description></item><item><title>New Payment Option: Amazon Pay</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-option-amazon-pay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/new-payment-option-amazon-pay/</guid><description>Lately we&amp;rsquo;ve received some feedback from our users asking for a credit card payment option. We hear you and we agree &amp;ndash; so today we&amp;rsquo;re introducing Amazon Pay for Textverified. We&amp;rsquo;ll also be adding Amazon Pay to PhoneBlur soon.
Amazon Pay is a great option for small bundle purchases if you don&amp;rsquo;t use crypto currency &amp;ndash; but since we&amp;rsquo;ll be processing payments through third party credit card companies, we do need to add a small percentage surcharge to any Amazon Pay purchases.</description></item><item><title>Flexible Purchases - A New Way to Verify</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/flexible-purchases-a-new-way-to-verify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/flexible-purchases-a-new-way-to-verify/</guid><description>Have you noticed that we&amp;rsquo;ve been making some changes lately here at Textverified? Today we wanted to let you know that we&amp;rsquo;re switching up our credits system to look more like dollars. Soon we&amp;rsquo;ll be taking the next logical step and simply calling your Textverified balance dollars. This shift will make it easy to keep track of your balance.
We&amp;rsquo;re also working on a flexible pricing plan to ensure you can buy exactly as much or as little as you need.</description></item><item><title>From Textverified to Phoneblur: Phone Number Rentals are Moving!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/from-textverified-to-phoneblur-phone-number-rentals-are-moving/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/from-textverified-to-phoneblur-phone-number-rentals-are-moving/</guid><description>Exciting news here at Textverified: phone number rentals are moving to our new service, Phoneblur. We have been hard at work bringing you a great new way to rent numbers &amp;ndash; and we even have an Android app!
We know you love Textverified, and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping you&amp;rsquo;ll love Phoneblur too. If you&amp;rsquo;re already familiar with renting phone numbers via Textverified, then you won&amp;rsquo;t notice too many changes over at Phoneblur.</description></item><item><title>Announcing Our New Android App!</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/updates/announcing-our-new-android-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/updates/announcing-our-new-android-app/</guid><description>Enjoy a native mobile experience while using the same great verifications you&amp;rsquo;ve always had &amp;ndash; check it out!
Whether you just need one verification or you need &amp;rsquo;em in bulk, we&amp;rsquo;ve got your back. Non-VoIP, US numbers at your fingertips &amp;ndash; now you can even keep your privacy on the go.
Let us know what you think and if there are any other features we can bring to our mobile app.</description></item></channel></rss>