<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Uber Eats on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/uber-eats/</link><description>Recent content in Uber Eats on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/uber-eats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get an Uber account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Uber is a widely used ride-sharing service that makes transportation convenient. During the sign-up process for Uber, phone number verification is a necessary step. Simplify this process with Textverified, offering real US-based numbers for secure verification without disclosing your personal number.
Choosing Textverified with Uber ensures the privacy of your personal phone number, adding an extra layer of security to your ride-sharing experience. This protection shields you from potential unwanted messages or privacy concerns.</description></item><item><title>Uber / UberEats Verifications</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-/-ubereats-verifications/</guid><description>To decrease the issues you face when doing Uber / UberEats verifications, especially with regards to already used numbers, please follow these steps:
After obtaining the number to use from Textverified, please go to https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source and enter the number in. If the number is already used, the https://auth.uber.com/login/?uber_client_name=eatsWebSignUp&amp;amp;source site will notify you and a verification code will not be sent: You can then report the number and try again with a new number.</description></item><item><title>Uber Eats &amp; DoorDash: Save on Food Delivery</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-eats-doordash-save-on-food-delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/uber-eats-doordash-save-on-food-delivery/</guid><description>Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find the time to cook. Food delivery apps are a great way to get a good meal and support your local restaurants. DoorDash and Uber Eats are two of the most popular food delivery services out there.
When you set-up a temporary phone number rental service on Textverified or Phoneblur, you can register for multiple accounts on DoorDash and Uber Eats. With multiple DoorDash and Uber Eats accounts, you can take advantage of all the available promotions.</description></item></channel></rss>