<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Uber on Textverified Blog</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/uber/</link><description>Recent content in Uber on Textverified Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.textverified.com/blog/tags/uber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get an Uber account without a phone number</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/how-to-get-an-uber-account-without-a-phone-number/</guid><description>Uber is a widely used ride-sharing service that makes transportation convenient. During the sign-up process for Uber, phone number verification is a necessary step. Simplify this process with Textverified, offering real US-based numbers for secure verification without disclosing your personal number.
Choosing Textverified with Uber ensures the privacy of your personal phone number, adding an extra layer of security to your ride-sharing experience. This protection shields you from potential unwanted messages or privacy concerns.</description></item><item><title>When to Use a Rental Number: Ride Shares</title><link>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.textverified.com/blog/when-to-use-a-rental-number-ride-shares/</guid><description>Many of our users have been wondering about different uses for rental numbers. Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about ride share services specifically.
Have you ever used Uber, Lyft, or even a ride share app for a traditional taxi company? Each of these services requires an active phone number before you can request a ride.
But if you use your personal phone number to register for a ride share app, then any driver who accepts your ride request will be able to see your number.</description></item></channel></rss>